▍2026 华盛顿 WTA500 半决赛
伊埃拉 6-4 6-2 大坂直美 · 赛后场上采访
Congratulations.
恭喜你
Your first ever WTA 500 final.
你生涯第一个 WTA 500 决赛
I got so many things to talk to you
我有一大堆问题想问你
about, but you were just looking up
但你刚才一直抬头看大屏
at that big board and watching the emotion
看着那一刻的情绪
between you and your coach
在你和你的教练之间
and your own self.
也在你自己心里
What does this moment mean to you?
这一刻对你意味着什么
O, I'm not sure yet.
我还说不上来
I think I'm still locked in.
我觉得我还在状态里
Like, I don't think it's over yet.
感觉这事儿还没结束
It's over. It's over.
结束了 已经结束了
one more match I guess.
那就还剩一场吧
But um super super happy.
但真的非常非常开心
I think I played really well
我觉得自己打得很好
and of course such a meaningful match
当然这也是一场很有分量的比赛
against a great player.
对手是一位了不起的球员
Um so really happy to share the court
所以能和大坂直美同场
with Naomi.
我真的很高兴
Yeah. Can I ask you you had a you
我能问一下吗 你们在网前
had a really lovely exchange there
有过一次很动人的交流
at the net.
就在球网边
Um and also you didn't show a lot
而且你赢下来的时候
of emotion when you won.
并没有表现出太多情绪
Can you just take me into the mindset
能不能带我进到你的心里
of what that meant to you
赢下这样一位对手
to to beat someone like her?
对你到底意味着什么
Yeah, like I said, it's such an honor
就像我说的 这是莫大的荣幸
to to share the court with her, but I think,
能和她同场 但我想
you know, it's with I guess just the way I
我猜跟我怎么面对这场球有关
approach today's match.
那种方式
Um, could never count her out,
你永远不能把她当成已经赢了
you know, and and like I said,
而且我刚才也说了
I was so I had to be so locked
我必须非常非常专注
in and I made it a point to be so locked
我是刻意让自己一直绷着
in, which is why until now I'm still
所以到现在我还没出
in that mode of of kind of competition.
那种比赛的状态里
So, uh, I need time to let it sink in.
我需要一点时间才消化得了
What about the support here?
那现场的支持呢
All week all week you
这一整周 整整一周
have been without a doubt
你毫无疑问是
the most popular player
最受欢迎的那位球员
that we have had on this court.
在这片场地上
It's been a phenomenal response
全场的反应好得惊人
from everybody.
所有人都是
What does that mean to you
这对你意味着什么
and how much did that help you today?
今天又帮了你多少
It helped me a lot.
帮了我特别多
I I'm happy
我很高兴
that you guys enjoyed the match
你们享受了这场比赛
or at least it it sounded like you did.
至少听起来是这样
Um I think there
我觉得有那么
was a really good couple points,
几分球 几次来回打得非常好
couple exchanges
几次交锋
which I think made it super exciting
让整场比赛特别精彩
and the level here in this tournament
而且这站赛事的水平
is really so high.
真的很高
We have the best of the best.
来的都是最好的球员
So you know
所以你知道
this tournament doesn't deserve anything
这样的赛事配得上
than the best fans.
最好的球迷
So the final Jessica Pegula,
那么决赛对手是佩古拉
she has won this tournament
她拿过这站的冠军
before many years ago.
很多年前了
You played her last year,
你去年跟她打过
a phenomenal three- set match in Miami.
在迈阿密 一场精彩的三盘大战
She just got you there.
她在那儿险胜了你
What can you do tomorrow to change
明天你能做点什么
that around?
把结果掉过来
H I'll have to ask my coach.
那我得问我的教练
He'll know best.
他最清楚
No, I'm joking.
开玩笑的
But um yeah,
不过说正经的话
I think I just have to trust myself.
我想我只需要相信自己
Uh I'm in the final for a reason.
我能站在决赛里是有原因的
She is such an amazing player also
她也是一位非常出色的球员
for a reason.
同样是有原因的
So I think it's going
所以我觉得这会是
to be a really good match.
一场很好的比赛